Guide to the Carl Djerassi Papers SC0348
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1999-021
  - Spectra Notebooks
    - Malik, Sohail. 1986 -1988. HPLC/GC. (Box 2)
    - Malik, Sohail. 1986 -1988. Mass Spec. (Box 2)
    - Malik, Sohail. 1986 -1988. NMR. (Box 2)
    - Spectra: III. HPLC/GC/Scint. (Box 2)
    - Unnamed. 1988. (Box 2)
    - Malik, Sohail. 1986 -1988. Mass Spec. (Box 3)
    - Malik, Sohail. 1986 -1988. NMR. (Box 3)
    - Spectra: II. HPLC/GCILScint. 1988 -1989. (Box 3)
    - Spectra: NMR I. 1990. (Box 3)
    - Spectra: NMR II. 1989. (Box 3)
    - Spectra: NMR VI. 1990. (Box 3)
    - Spectra: NMR VII. 1990 -1991. (Box 3)
    - Rabirowitz. Mass Spectra. 1987 -1991. (Box 4)
    - Spectra: IV. HPLC/GC/LS. 1990 -1991. (Box 4)
    - Spectra: NMR I. 1987 -1991. (Box 4)
    - Spectra: NMR II. 1988 -1990. (Box 4)
    - Spectra: NMR IV. 1989 -1990. (Box 4)
  - Lab and Sprectra notebooks
    - Cholestadienols (Box 5)
    - Eserayanoglu (Box 5)
    - Mass Spec. Data Notebooks 260, 263 and 265 (Box 5)
    - NMR Spectra Lab Notebooks 260,265,225 (Box 5)
    - Rohmer (Box 5)
    - HPLC and GC traces 265, 257, to notebook 263 (Box 6)
    - HPLC and GC traces of Marine Sterol Mixtures (Box 6)
    - NMR Spectra Lab Notebooks 265 & 263, 265 -246 -I (Box 6)
    - Program and Computer Notes (Box 6)
  - Djerassi Reprints, By Number
    - Reprints 1 -555 (Box 7)
    - Reprints 556 -1071 (Box 8)
    - Reprints 1072 -1192 (Box 9, Folder 1-8)
    - Index to Reprints (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Grants/Research
    - Expired grants, financial files: Steroids, Marine chemistry (Box 9, Folder 10-31)
    - Expired grants, financial files: National Science Foundation, Marine chemistry (Box 9, Folder 32-36)
    - Expired grants, financial files: National Science Foundation, circular dichroism of cyclic ketones (Box 9, Folder 37-38)
    - Expired grants, financial files: National Science Foundation, magnetic circular dichroism of forbidden transitions in organic molecules (Box 9, Folder 39-40)
    - Expired grants, financial files: Mass spectrometry, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 1-15)
    - Expired grants, financial files: Magnetic circular dichroism, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 16-31)
    - Expired grants, financial files: DENDRAL -artificial intelligence (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Expired grants, financial files: Miscellaneous, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 33-36)
    - Expired grants, financial files: Miscellaneous, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous financial files (lab fees, cell biology vax service center, petty cash, etc.) (Box 11, Folder 6-11)
    - Expired grants, financial files: Steroid studies, 1972-73, and Mass spectrometry, 1964-75 (Box 11, Folder 12-26)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence concerning grants, proposals, etc. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Resource related research: computers and chemistry, 1971-75 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - NSF Research proposal "Carbon-13 Nuclear Magnetic Resonance of Steroids " (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Stanford chemistry department, research instrument proposal 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - NSF miscellaneous correspondence (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - California sea grant college program (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Univ. of Minnesota; electronic structure and stereochemistry of hemoglobins (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - DENDRAL exit procedures (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Resource related research: computers and chemistry, 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2001-125
  - Correspondence files with students and colleagues, including research results, typescripts of articles, etc., 1970s-80s
    - Back, Thomas G. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Blanc, Pierre-Alain (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Block, John (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bohlin, Lars (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bonini, Carlo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Crist, Vincent (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Eggersdorfer, Manfred (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Eggert, Hanne (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Gebreyesus, Tarekegn (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Goldbeck, Robert (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gunatilaka, A. A. Leslile (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Hale, Ronnie Lee (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - High, Le Roy B. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hirano, Yutaka (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Jagodzinska, Barbara (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - James, Anthony N. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Jiang, Xiang-Yu [empty] (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Jiang, Yianhao [empty] (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Kapoor, A. L. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Karpf, Martin (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Kehres, Lisa (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Khalil, Wahid (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Kho-Wiseman, Ernest (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Kokke, Wilhemus (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Kurtz, Kara [empty] (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Kutney, James P. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Lance, James (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Lang, Robert (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Levy, Dr. Jean (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Li, Xian (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Li, Lian-Niang (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Lindberg, James (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Liang, Yi (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Mauli, Rolf (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Mors, Walter (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Nakano, T. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Pak, Chwang Siek (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Povov, S. S. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Rohmer, Michel (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Roller, Peter P. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Rothberg, Irvin (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Shamma, Maurice (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Sheik, Younus M. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Smith, Glen (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Sjostrand, Ulf (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Steinbach, Rainer (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Steiner, Eric (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Tan, Wai Lee (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Tarchini, Claudio (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Tecon, Pierre (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Theobald, Norbert (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Villotti, Riccardo (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Walkup, Robert D. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Yang, Shi-Ying (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Zielinski, Jan (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence files
    - Industrial Affiliates, 1987-89 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Industrial Affiliates, 1980-87 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Industrial Affiliates, miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - International Center of Insect Physiology and Ecology (ICIPE), 1980-85 [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - (ICIPE), 1980-85 [2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - (ICIPE), 1976-79 [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - (ICIPE), 1976-79 [2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - (ICIPE), 1975-76 [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - (ICIPE), 1975-76 [2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - (ICIPE), 1968-74 [1 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - (ICIPE), 1968-74 [2 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - (ICIPE), 1968-74 [3 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - (ICIPE), 1968-74 [4 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - International Organization for Chemical Sciences in Development (IOCD), 1984-87 [1 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - (IOCD), 1984-87 [2 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - (IOCD), 1984-87 [3 of 3] (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Japan Spectroscopic Co., Ltd., 1968-82 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Japan Spectroscopic Co., Ltd., 1965-68 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Japan Spectroscopic Co., Ltd., 1961-64 [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Japan Spectroscopic Co., Ltd., 1961-64 [2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Johnson Symposium 1985-89 [1 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Johnson Symposium 1985-89 [2 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Johnson Symposium 1985-89 [3 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Johnson Symposium 1985-89 [4 of 4] (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Le Men – Vobtusine (correspondence with J. Poisson), 1962-65 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Jean Le Men and M. M. Janot, 1963-82 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Jean Le Men and M. M. Janot, 1956-62 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Magnetic Circular Dichroism [1 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Magnetic Circular Dichroism [2 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Magnetic Circular Dichroism [3 of 3] (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Marine Chemistry (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Marine Chemistry – Artic (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Marine products (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 1973-78 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 1961-72 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - NAS: U.S.-Brazil Graduate Program in Chemistry, 1968-73 [1 of 4] (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - NAS: U.S.-Brazil Graduate Program in Chemistry, 1968-73 [2 of 4] (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - NAS: U.S.-Brazil Graduate Program in Chemistry, 1968-73 [3 of 4] (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - NAS: U.S.-Brazil Graduate Program in Chemistry, 1968-73 [4 of 4] (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - NAS: U.S.-Brazil Graduate Program in Chemistry, 1974-75 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - NAS: U.S.-Brazil Graduate Program in Chemistry, 1976-79 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - NAS: U.S.-Brazil Workshop, 1967-71 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - NAS: LASB material pertaining to Colombia [1 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - NAS: LASB material pertaining to Colombia [2 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - NAS: LASB material pertaining to Peru (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - NAS: Commission on International Relations, 1974-75 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - NAS: Egypt (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - NAS: Ethiopia (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - NAS: Congo, 1976-88 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - NAS: Congo, 1974-76 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - NAS: Congo, 1973-74 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - NAS: Congo, 1972 Dec. – June (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - NAS: Congo, 1972 May – Dec. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - NAS: Congo, 1971 Aug. –1972 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - NAS: Congo, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - NAS: Chemistry publications in Proceedings, 1964-72 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - NAS: Sri Lanka Workshop June 1975 [1 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - NAS: Sri Lanka Workshop June 1975 [2 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - NAS: Tanzania Program (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - NAS: Argentine Workshop, 1968-75 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - NAS: Latin America Science Board, 1967-68 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - NAS: Latin America Science Board, 1965-67 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - NAS: Nomination for presidency (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - NAS: Board on Science and Technology for International Development, 1983-88 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - NAS: Board on Science and Technology for International Development, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - NAS: Board on Science and Technology for International Development, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - NAS: Board on Science and Technology for International Development, 1967-75 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Organic Mass Spectroscopy, Journal of, 1967-86 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Pugwash Conferences, 1974-86 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Pugwash Conferences, 1973-74 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Pugwash Conferences, Munich, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Pugwash Conferences, Warsaw, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - World Health Organization, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - World Health Organization, 1975-78 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - World Health Organization, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - World Health Organization, 1971-75 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Personnel records: correspondence, appointments, letters of reference, etc., 1950s-1990s
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted for 75 years.
    - Anderson, Gary D. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Back, Thomas G. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Balasingam, Prashanthi (Gee) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bannick, Mark (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Barefoot, Mrs. Annemarie (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Barth, Gunter (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Beechan, Curtis Michael (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Beereboom, John (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Bladocha-Moreau, Michele (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Blanc, Pierre-Alain (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Blossey, Erich C. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bohlin, Lars (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Bonini, Carlo (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Braekman, J. C. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Briat, Dr. Bernard (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown, Frederick J. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Keith S., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Budzikiewicz, Herbert (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Bunnenberg, Edward (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Burke, Basil Anthony (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Carballeira, Mestor M. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Carlson, Robert M. K. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Catalan, Cesar A. N. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Chamberlin, James Wesley (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Chan, Andrea (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Cheer, Clair James (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Cooper, Christopher (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Corbo, Joe (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Crabbe, Pierre (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Crandell, Christopher (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Crist, B. Vincent (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Dageforde, Mary (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Dawson, John (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - De Amicis, Carl (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Delseth, Claude (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Demirev, Plamen (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Dias, Jerry Ray (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Diekman, John d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dillon, Diane M. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Dixon, (James) Scott (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Dolinger, Peter M. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Donald, Alfield (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Do-Trong, My (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dow, William C. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Duffield, Alan (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Eadon, George A. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Edgar, Mark (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Egli, Huldrych (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Eggersdorfer, Manfred (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Eggert, Hanne (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Eisenbraun, E. J. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Elder, Danny L. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Exman, Iankel (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Fella, Andrea (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Figdor, Sanford K. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Ford (Finch), Neville (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Fowle, Stephen (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Gallegos, Maria Elena (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Goldsmith, David (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Gaete-Holmes, Richard (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - George, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Gerspacher, Marc (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Ghirardelli, Dr. Robert G. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Gilbert, Dr. Benjamin (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Gimmy, Barbara (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Gore, J. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Gorthey, Lee Ann (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Grant, Barbara Dianne (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Gray, Neil A. (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Green, Mark M. (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Gritter, Roy J. (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Groves, Kathy (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Gulacar, O. Fazil (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Gurst, Jerome E. (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Haley, Michael (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Hall, Karen (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Hammerum, Steen (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Harel, Zvi (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Harris, Ralph N., III (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Hirano, Sakiko (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Hirano, Yutaka (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Hoberg, Max (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Huang, Liang (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Ikeda, Dr. Masazumi (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Itoh, Toshihiro (became Toshihiro Akihisa, 1984) (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Jaeger, David A. (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Jagodzinska, Barbara (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - James, A. N. (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Jiang, Xiang-Yu (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Jiang, Yianhao (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Joseph, Jackiel (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Karpf, Martin (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Keegan, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Kehres, Lisa (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Khalil, Dr. M. Wahid (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Kho-Wiseman, Ernest (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Knierzinger, Andreas (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Knudsen-Smith, Kathy (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Koch, Patrick (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Kohrman, Michael H. (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Kokke, Dr. Wilhelmus C. M. C. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Konopelski, Joseph P. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Kurtz, Kara (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Krakower, Gerald W. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kramar, Jaroslav (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Kutney, James P. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Lance, James (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Lang, Robert W. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Lankelma, Jan (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Lavanchy, Andre (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Lawson, Mishelle (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Lee, Maggie (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Lee, Shy-Fuh (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Leeming, Peter R. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Li, Mr. Hui-Ding (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Li, Lian-Niang (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Li, Xian (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Liang, Yi (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Lightner, David A. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Lindberg, James G. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Linder, Robert (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Lindley, Matthew Robert (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Ling, Nicholas Chi-Kwan (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Lockyer, Ellen (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Lu, Yu-Cheng (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Luo, Fen-Tair Frank (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - MacLeod, John K. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Marekov, Nikolai (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Massey, Ian J. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - McCallum, Stuart (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Mena, Philippe (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Midgley, Ian (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Mills, John S. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Mitscher, Lester A. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Moldowan, J. Michael (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Monteiro, Hugo J. (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Muccino, Richard R. (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Nakano, Tatsuhiko (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Newton, Geoff (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Nichols, Linda (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Nordstrom, Carla (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Nourse, James (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Nussbaum, Alex (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Pak, Dr. Chwang Siek (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Park, Chong Ok (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Patterson, Donald G. Jr. (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Perry, Guynn (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Pettit, George R. (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Pilet, Olivier (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Popov, Simeon Simeonov (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Proudfoot, John (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Raederstorff, Daniel (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Rasak, Jon (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Records, Ruth (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Rice, Peter (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Rider, Mary (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Robertson, Dr. A. V. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Rohmer, Michel (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Savage, Dorothy (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Schooley, David A. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Schwenzer, Gretchen M. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Seidel, Pei Chuan (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Sengupta, Pasupati (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Shamma, Maurice (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Sheikh, M. Younus (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Shu, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Shulman, Michelle (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Simek, Jan (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Sing, Yuen-Lung Lawrence (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Singy, Gerard (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Sjoberg, Berndt (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Sjostrand, Ulf I. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Dennis H. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Smith, Glenn (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Prof. Grant G. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Howard E. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Spangler, Richard J. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Steinbach, Rainer (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Steiner, Eric (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Sugnaux, Francois (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Sundararaman, P. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Suyat, Reginald (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Tan, Wai Lee (Mrs. Wong) (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Tarchini, Dr. Claudio (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Taylor, Evelyn (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Tecon, Pierre (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Theobald, Norbert (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Tokes, Laszlo (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Tomer, Kenneth (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Trudell, James R. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Uedelhoven, Wolfgang (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Undheim, Kjell (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Van Antwerp, Craig (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Vanderah, David J. (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Van Horn, Albert R. (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Varkony, Tomas Haim (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Veizades, Nicholas (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Waespe-Sarcevic, Nada (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Wee, Andrew Guan Hin (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Weidler, Anne-Marie (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Weinberg, David S. (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Wellman, Keith M. (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Wenger, Jacques (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Westley, John W. (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Wiersig, James R. (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Wiley, Dr. Richard H. (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Wilkinson, David I. (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Wilson, John Miller (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Withers, Dr. Nancy Wallis (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Woodgate, Paul D. (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Wu, Irene (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Yang, Shi-Ying (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Yeo, Adrian Ning Hong (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Zalkow, Leon (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Zeeh, Dr. Bernd (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Zielinski, Jan (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Optical Rotary Dispersion; Applications to Organic Chemistry (McGraw Hill), 1960; Accession ARCH-2002-335 (Box 1)
- Additional Material
  - Paul Klee: New to the Djerassi Collection at SFMOMA (flyer)
  - American Chemical Society Presidential Session-Honoring Carl Djerassi, 2006 Sep 10
- Additional material, 1966, 2014; Accession ARCH-2015-032
  - A Corporation and a molecule, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Beyond Chemistry: The Last 25 years of a Nonagenarian, 2014-01-30; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Carl Djerassi: Beyond Chemistry: The Last 25 years of a Nonagenarian, January 30, 2014, Clark Center Auditorium, Stanford University, 3:00 pm
    A celebration of Carl Djerassi's 90th Birthday Year Recognized worldwide as a leader in science, Carl Djerassi's achievements have spanned numerous decades. He has received the National Medal of Science, the National Medal of Technology, the Priestly Medal, and the first Wolf Prize in chemistry. He is the chemical "Father of the Pill" and has published 1,200 scientific papers, five novels, five non-fiction books, 11 plays, poetry, essays, and short stories. He has 32 honorary degrees. Dr. Djerassi's full biography is available at title="Homepage">http://www.djerassi.com/
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH_2016_009
  - SMIP Ranch Subject Files--A:C (Box 1)
  - SMIP Ranch Subject Files--C (Box 2)
  - SMIP Ranch Subject Files--C (Box 3)
  - SMIP Ranch Subject Files--D:L (Box 4)
  - SMIP Ranch Subject Files--M-W (Box 5)
  - Personnel--A:R (Box 6)
  - Personnel--R:Z (Box 7)
  - Subject Files (Box 8)
  - Publications--1:250 (Box 9)
  - Publications--251:616 (Box 10)
  - Publications--617:752 (Box 11)
  - Publications--754:885 (Box 12)
  - Publications--754:885 (Box 13)
  - Misc (Box 14)
  - Misc (Box 15)
  - Speeches, 1973-1991 (Box 16)
  - Speeches, 1992-1996 (Box 17)
  - Speeches, 1997-2008 (Box 18)
  - Publications--850:970 (Box 19)
  - Publications--971-1030 (Box 20)
  - Publications--1031-1085 (Box 21)
  - Teaching (Box 22)
  - Publications--1086-1144 (Box 23)
  - Publications--1145-1189 (Box 24)
  - Publications--1190-1212 (Box 25)
  - Publications--1212-1213; Birth Control (Box 26)
  - Birth Control (Box 27)
  - Teaching (Hum Bio 150), 1972-1976 (Box 28)
  - Teaching (Hum Bio 150), 1974-1981 (Box 29)
  - Teaching (Hum Bio 150), 1982-1987 (Box 30)
  - Teaching (Hum Bio 150), 1993-1996 (Box 31)
  - Teaching (Hum Bio 150), 1987-1993 (Box 32)
  - Conferences (Box 33)
  - Conferences (Box 34)
  - Correspondence--A:B (Box 35)
  - Correspondence--B:C (Box 36)
  - Correspondence--C:D (Box 37)
  - Correspondence--D:F (Box 38)
  - Correspondence--G:H (Box 39)
  - Correspondence--H:J (Box 40)
  - Correspondence--J:L (Box 41)
  - Correspondence--L:M (Box 42)
  - Correspondence--M:N (Box 43)
  - Correspondence--N:P (Box 44)
  - Correspondence--P:R (Box 45)
  - Correspondence--R:S (Box 46)
  - Biographical Files (Box 47)
  - Computer Files (Box 48)
  - Personnel (Box 49)
  - Chemistry Department; Hum Bio (Box 50)
  - Hum Bio; Contraception (Box 51)
  - Correspondence--S (Box 52)
  - Correspondence--S:T (Box 53)
  - Correspondence--T:W (Box 54)
  - Correspondence--W (Box 55)
  - Correspondence--Z; Literary Publications and Reviews (Box 56)
  - Literary Publications and Reviews (Box 57)
  - Literary Publications and Reviews; Rolodex (Box 58)
  - Syntex Publications--1:395 (Box 59)
  - Syntex Publications--396- (Box 60)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2016-047
  - Computer Hard Drive, 1 hard drive(s) (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2016-096
  - "The Adolescent Patient: Gynecology, Sexuality-Contraception, Pregnancy", circa 1980 (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2016-142
  - Figures re Fatty Acids (Box 1)
  - Poster - Une immaculate Miss Conception, Theatre Du Grutli, Geneve, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Poster - Wie haben Sie das gemacht, Herr Djerassi? Siemens, 1999 (Box 2)